<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Lessons in...</title><link>https://khongsao.github.io/blog/</link><description>Recent content on Lessons in...</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 Oct 2021 01:40:52 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://khongsao.github.io/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Will the Korean Flavour Last?</title><link>https://khongsao.github.io/blog/kdrama/kdmynamecry/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Oct 2021 01:40:52 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://khongsao.github.io/blog/kdrama/kdmynamecry/</guid><description>Surely you cannot be penalised for having been exposed to all things Korea for over 10 years. As soon as the knives and short hair came out I started singing Cry Cry. The cigarette at the wake gave it away. A nice show but too much of a rehash of Tara&amp;rsquo;s Cry Cry in 2011. There are many people jumping on the K drama bandwagon post SG, hopefully this will not lead to a bastardisation of the industry.</description></item><item><title>Korean Dramas: Where to being?</title><link>https://khongsao.github.io/blog/kdrama/kdwhere2begin/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Oct 2021 21:14:30 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://khongsao.github.io/blog/kdrama/kdwhere2begin/</guid><description>Wow you watched Squid Games God Tier Crash Landing on You (2019) Goblin (2016) King: Eternal Monarch (2020) Rooftop Prince (2012) Miss You (2012) Big (2012) Very Good Itaewon Class (2020) Hell is Other People (2019) Signal (2016) Live (2018) Taxi Driver (2021) There&amp;rsquo;s Something in the Rain (2018) Yumi&amp;rsquo;s Cells (2021) Did not live up to expectation / Died out AKA Shows containing Bae Suzy Vagabond (2019) Squid Games (2021) Start Up (2020) Sisyphus: The Myth (2021) Mouse (2021) To decide</description></item><item><title>Yumi's Cells</title><link>https://khongsao.github.io/blog/kdrama/yumiscells/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Oct 2021 21:14:30 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://khongsao.github.io/blog/kdrama/yumiscells/</guid><description>Love from Within A solid romance drama with an original concept. Inspired from a Webtoon the protagonist Kim Yumi has her anthropomorphised cells on show ranging from Huger Cell to Lust Cell. Yumis-Cells.jpg</description></item><item><title>Hell Is Other People</title><link>https://khongsao.github.io/blog/kdrama/kdhell/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2021 23:07:37 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://khongsao.github.io/blog/kdrama/kdhell/</guid><description>The Grim Reaper Reaps</description></item><item><title>Newblog</title><link>https://khongsao.github.io/blog/newblog/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Oct 2021 23:23:07 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://khongsao.github.io/blog/newblog/</guid><description>#test text for New blog</description></item><item><title>Teaching History</title><link>https://khongsao.github.io/blog/teaching/sywt-teach/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Mar 2021 19:37:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://khongsao.github.io/blog/teaching/sywt-teach/</guid><description>How should we be teaching history? Reasons The Usual Suspects Broaden horizons Show how society changes Reality We are passing on the torch of Human history.
Content Methods American West WW1 Medicine Elizabeth [[American West Lessons]] [[WW1 Lessons]] [[Medicine Lessons]] [[Elizabeth Lessons]] [[Model GCSE answers American West]] [[Model GCSE Answers WW1]] [[Model GCSE Answers Medicine]] [[Model GCSE Answers Elizabeth]]</description></item><item><title>16 Marker</title><link>https://khongsao.github.io/blog/teaching/16marker/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2021 13:40:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://khongsao.github.io/blog/teaching/16marker/</guid><description>So just what are these factors? They are timeless themes that run throughout our course. It doesn&amp;rsquo;t matter if we are talking about medieval times, early modern, 19th century or the modern era - factors make an appearance in each one - When we look at the course as a whole it is clear that some factors make more of an impact and are more prominent in certain time periods than other.</description></item><item><title>Guide to Teaching</title><link>https://khongsao.github.io/blog/teaching/teachingguide/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2021 00:40:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://khongsao.github.io/blog/teaching/teachingguide/</guid><description>Caveats This information is provided as a collection of random pointers that have worked well for me over the years This list is meant not as a checklist but merely pointers that have helped in and around school Some, most or all of which you may not agree with In the Classroom Wait for silence Fill a spray bottle with water, keep your whiteboard clean Have pupils perform tasks, hand out books, clean your room Number seats and books, helps with hands down questioning and book distribution When taking books in, have students open them at exactly where you will be marking Working with technology Printing - learn how to scan and leave a post for people Have a collection of coloured paper next to the printer for SEND Create email templates for typical emails such as detentions, reprographics and parents Control Q on SIMS Control Shift V will paste without formatting Keep records, establish a habit of scanning work - Working with colleagues Do not gossip If parents Outside school There will come times when you meet pupils outside of school, and for the most part it will be a smile nod, a smile or some other for of acknowledgment.</description></item><item><title>True Beauty2</title><link>https://khongsao.github.io/blog/kdrama/truebeauty/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2021 22:39:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://khongsao.github.io/blog/kdrama/truebeauty/</guid><description> Love Triangle Academics Beauty Peer Pressure Is love worth dying for? We all have inner demons
Squid Games</description></item><item><title>Turn over your wrists</title><link>https://khongsao.github.io/blog/posts/turn-over-your-wirst/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Feb 2021 22:39:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://khongsao.github.io/blog/posts/turn-over-your-wirst/</guid><description>Quote 1) Seneca Can you no longer see a road to freedom? It&amp;rsquo;s right in front of you. You need only turn over your wrists.
Quote 2) 4chan &amp;ldquo;I never got my people would kill themselves So if you want to die you obviously don&amp;rsquo;t give a shit. Like, about anyone. Because if there is anyone who loves you, you don&amp;rsquo;t give a fuck about them, or hurting them, and if there is not, there is no one to give a shit about.</description></item><item><title>Itaewon Class</title><link>https://khongsao.github.io/blog/kdrama/itaweonclass/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Jan 2021 00:40:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://khongsao.github.io/blog/kdrama/itaweonclass/</guid><description>How to get revenge&amp;hellip; wait and then wait some more Take a peak into the social status hiearchy Yangban. On another day you think you could be watching the revenge tail from Parasite</description></item><item><title>Girl With Seven Names</title><link>https://khongsao.github.io/blog/books/girlwith7names/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://khongsao.github.io/blog/books/girlwith7names/</guid><description> Author Reading Status: Read Date Finished July 1st, 2020 Why North Korean defector account</description></item><item><title>Life in the Trenches</title><link>https://khongsao.github.io/blog/teaching/itsoct2021/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://khongsao.github.io/blog/teaching/itsoct2021/</guid><description>Please work it has been a long time since i had some joy! Trench Life The everyday routine When soldiers were not fighting, they lived a rather boring life in the trenches. They rotated duties in front. line trenches which meant that one third of the men were on guard duty while another third repaired the trench and collected food water, letters, ammunition and first aid supplies. The other third would rest.</description></item><item><title>Madness of Crowds</title><link>https://khongsao.github.io/blog/books/madnessofcrowds/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://khongsao.github.io/blog/books/madnessofcrowds/</guid><description>Author Douglas Murray Reading Status: Read Date Finished July 1st, 2020 Why Fan of the author. How society interacts Tags:: #Book #woke #gender #race #identity #gay #sexuality #interaction #InterpersonalRelationships #norms #truth #socialmedia #bias Key Highlight:: - &amp;ldquo;‘[[Identity politics]]’, meanwhile, has become the place where social justice finds its caucuses. It atomizes society into different interest groups according to sex (or #gender), #race, sexual preference and more.</description></item><item><title>Show Your Work</title><link>https://khongsao.github.io/blog/books/showyourwork/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://khongsao.github.io/blog/books/showyourwork/</guid><description>Key Take Aways</description></item><item><title>Tech and Teaching</title><link>https://khongsao.github.io/blog/teaching/bp-t-techteach/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://khongsao.github.io/blog/teaching/bp-t-techteach/</guid><description>Remember that CPD day, the one where the member of SLT had chosen to link a YouTube video in the PPT? Remember when the URL was clicked. Remember how, because it was in presentation mode the browser of the day (it was IE, let’s be real) played the video behind the Presentation? I do.
I do because said member of staff was then at a loss for several minutes, for me it was an epoch, as to why there was sound but no video.</description></item><item><title>Theme Demo</title><link>https://khongsao.github.io/blog/teaching/theme-demo/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://khongsao.github.io/blog/teaching/theme-demo/</guid><description>Style Demo h1 Heading h2 Heading h3 Heading h4 Heading h5 Heading h6 Heading This is bold text
This is bold text
This is italic text
This is italic text
Deleted text
This is text with inline math $\sum_{n=1}^{\infty} 2^{-n} = 1$ and with math blocks:
$$ \sum_{n=1}^{\infty} 2^{-n} = 1 $$
Heading Another heading text text text text text text Block quotes are written like so.</description></item><item><title>Me?</title><link>https://khongsao.github.io/blog/about/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://khongsao.github.io/blog/about/</guid><description>So I am Chris On this site you will find my blog pertaining to teaching, society and my experiences
You will also find my notes and musing on a range of books, mostly non fiction
Thoughts and musings on Kdramas will also be discussed in the hope of converting more people away from Western Cinema
If any of the content has been helpful, feel free to Monzo Me a coffee</description></item><item><title>The Count of Monte Cristo</title><link>https://khongsao.github.io/blog/books/countofmonte/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://khongsao.github.io/blog/books/countofmonte/</guid><description>I am not saying That you should seek revenge That you should use escape from prison This was a long read, set aside a good summer or, let&amp;rsquo;s be honest, a number of hours on Audible (52 to be precise at x1 speed). This was an education in place names - there really are some books that are just off-putting, and I think if I hadn&amp;rsquo;t sped through the first chapter at x2 speed I would have put the book down.</description></item></channel></rss>