<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on Lessons in...</title><link>https://khongsao.github.io/blog/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on Lessons in...</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2021 20:54:16 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://khongsao.github.io/blog/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The White Liberal</title><link>https://khongsao.github.io/blog/posts/malcolmx/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2021 20:54:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://khongsao.github.io/blog/posts/malcolmx/</guid><description>The white liberal is the worst enemy to America, and the worst enemy to the black man. Let me explain what I mean by the white liberal. In America there is no such thing as Democrat or Republican anymore. In America you have liberals and conservatives. The only people living in the past who think in terms of I’m a Democrat or Republican, is the American Negro. He’s the one that runs around bragging about party affiliation.</description></item><item><title>Tech and Teaching</title><link>https://khongsao.github.io/blog/posts/my-first-post/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://khongsao.github.io/blog/posts/my-first-post/</guid><description>Remember that CPD day, the one where the member of SLT had chosen to link a YouTube video in the PPT? Remember when the URL was clicked. Remember how, because it was in presentation mode the browser of the day (it was IE, let’s be real) played the video behind the Presentation? I do.
I do because said member of staff was then at a loss for several minutes, for me it was an epoch, as to why there was sound but no video.</description></item><item><title>Theme Demo</title><link>https://khongsao.github.io/blog/posts/theme-demo/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://khongsao.github.io/blog/posts/theme-demo/</guid><description>Style Demo h1 Heading h2 Heading h3 Heading h4 Heading h5 Heading h6 Heading This is bold text
This is bold text
This is italic text
This is italic text
Deleted text
This is text with inline math $\sum_{n=1}^{\infty} 2^{-n} = 1$ and with math blocks:
$$ \sum_{n=1}^{\infty} 2^{-n} = 1 $$
Heading Another heading text text text text text text Block quotes are written like so.</description></item></channel></rss>